# Bushra Aljasem

Computer Engineer

#### Contact

#### **Address**

Turkey / Ankara, 06050

#### **Phone**

+905388245278

#### E-mail

bushra.aljasseem@gmail.co

#### LinkedIn

https://www.linkedin.com/in/bushra-aljasem-7998171

#### **www**

https://bushajsm.github.ic/portfolio/

## **Skills**

PHP/ Laravel-Codeigniter

Excellent

Javascript/ NodeJS /Express

Excellent

C# / ASP.NET

Good

Vue is / vuex /Vutify / Axios

Excellent

HTML5/CSS3

Excellent

React is / Redux

Well-qualified Full Stack Developer familiar with various programming utilities and languages. Knowledgeable of backend and frontend development requirements. Handles any part of the process with ease. Collaborative team player with excellent technical abilities offering 5 years of related experience.

### **Work History**

2022-03 -2022-07

### **Web Application Specialist**

Tailor Made Excel, London

- Collaborated with the web team to establish projects goals, projections and milestones.
- Designed, implemented and monitored web pages, plugins and functionality for continuous improvement.
- Develop application programming interface (API) for web apps.
- Related Experience (Laravel-VueJS)

2021-01 -2022-03

## Full Stack Web Developer

Nanomedya Digital Agency, Ankara

- Developed efficient and maintainable software according to business objectives and needs of clients.
- Used WordPress CMS to develop Seo-friendly Websites.
- Build WordPress themes from scratch according to clients' needs.
- Reviewed code, debugged problems and corrected issues
- Discussed project progress with customers, collected feedback on different stages and directly addressed concerns.
- Related Experience (Wordpress-Express-Codeigniter-Laravel-Bootstrap)

2019-07 -2021-01

### **Full Stack Web Developer**

Birbölüiki IT Agency, Ankara

 Planned website development, converting mockups into usable web presence with HTML, CSS, JavaScript, and Related frameworks such as

Very Good Bootstrap /Tailwind / Material UI **Excellent** Mysal / MongoDB Excellent **RESTFUL API** Excellent JSON Web Token (JWT) Excellent **TypeScript** Very Good Ajax Very Good C panel Very Good Languages Arabic

Arabic

Excellent

English

Very Good

Turkish

Excellent

Bootstrap Tailwind, React is, Vue is.

- Alternated between frontend and backend development duties, fulfilling Full Stack development commitments on company projects.
- Related Experience (Express-Laravel-ReactJS-VueJS)

2018-01 -2019-01

### **Junior Web Developer**

ARTMENTAL Agency, Ankara

- Maintained advanced knowledge of several programming languages.
- Built website interfaces with HTML and CSS.
- Developed layouts that met the user expectations.
- Applied knowledge of JavaScript and Object-Oriented Programming to create successful interactive designs.
- Built and styled new mobile-friendly websites, transitioning legacy presentations to simultaneous easy-to-use versions.
- Related Experience (Express-React-Laravel-VueJS-Bootstap)

2014-09 -2016-12

## **Software Engineer**

Syrian Ministry Of Tourism, Damascus

- E-government portal development.
- Participated in architecture, design and implementation of back-end features using C# Language.
- Related Experience (ASP.NET-SQL Server)

### **Education**

2017-01 -2020-01

## Master's Degree: Computer Engineering

Kırıkkale Üniversitesi - Kırıkkale/ Turkey

- Security in IOT Networks Thesis
- IoT Security Issues, Threats, and Defenses
- 3.25 GPA

2009-01 -2014-01

## **Bachelor's Degree: Computer Engineering**

Ittihad University - Damascus / Syria

- Bachelor's degree in Computer engineering
- 3.15 GPA